Yeah the GOAT is LeBron
Yeah
He got Bronny, he got Bryce, what you want?
He got all the skills, oh and plus he's handsome
I know that he's the GOAT, I ain't dumb
The greatest in the pros, he is really one-of-one
The GOAT is LeBron
He's always showin' up, we call him LeSunshine
All his three-point shots light up like a lantern
It's Lakers in five, hang another banner
He's the two-three god, yeah the GOAT is LeBron
He got rings, he got shoes, that's a lot
The people always praising every day from dusk to dawn
When the laser's pointed down at you, who you want?
They said that they want Iguodala, well I want LeBron
He had two sons and taught 'em how to ball just like The One
Just a kid from Akron, I know that he's really chosen
LeBron you are my hero, you're the king, you're number one
What would I do without you, I can't stand to be alone
He got a lot of trophies piling up inside the case
Nico gave us Luka so we can ring chase
LeBron you are the greatest yeah I do not mean to glaze
I promise I will always love you, LeBron James